<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!-- TODO add some more. -->
    <string-array name="workout_list">
        <item>Abs</item>
        <item>Bicep (Arm)</item>
        <item>Calf (Leg)</item>
        <item>Chest</item>
        <item>Forearm</item>
        <item>Hamstring (Leg)</item>
        <item>Lats (Back)</item>
        <item>Quadricep (Leg)</item>
        <item>Shoulder</item>
        <item>Trapezius (Back)</item>
        <item>Tricep (Arm)</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="workout_instructions">
        <item name="leg_raise">What you\'ll need: Somewhere to lay down (bench or pull-up bar optional).\n\nWhat to do:
            Keep your lower back in contact with the floor and your legs together. Slowly raise them
            to a 45 degree angle, and return to the starting position.\n\nHow to switch it up: If you\'ve
            got a pull up bar or something similar, you can perform the same exercises while hanging.
            This is generally considered more difficult than when performed seated or lying down.</item>
        <item name="bicep_curl">What you\'ll need: A barbell or dumbbells.\n\nWhat to do: Start with your arms fully
            extended, slowly bringing them up towards your body. Slowly return to the position in
            which you started. That\'s it!</item>
        <item name="calf_raise">What you\'ll need: Your legs (machine or dumbbells optional).\n\nWhat to do: If you
            don\'t have a machine available, find a small ledge elevated a few inches above the floor.
            Stand with your toes on the edge, and slowly raise up to stand on your tip-toes. Return
            to the position in which you started. The technique is the same if using a machine.</item>
        <item name="benchpress">What you\'ll need: A bench and a barbell (or dumbbells).\n\nWhat to do: Lay on your back
            on the bench, with your arms slightly more than shoulder width apart and the barbell
            above your chest. Lift, extending your arms all the way (CAREFUL not to lock your elbows!).
            Lower the weight to chest level and repeat.\n\nHow you can switch it up: Use an incline or
            decline bench. This will emphasise the upper and lower pectoral (chest) respectively. Use
            a narrower grip to more emphasise the triceps (back of the arm)</item>
        <item name="forearm_curl">What you\'ll need: A bench or similar surface, and a barbell
            (or dumbbells).\n\nWhat to do: rest your arm on the bench with your hand extended over the
            edge, palm facing up. Start with your wrist fully extended (fingers pointing towards
            the floor), and raise your hand as far as possible. Slowly return to starting position.</item>
        <item name="stiff_deadlift">What you\'ll need: A barbell.\n\nWhat to do: Stand behind the barbell, and
            grip it with your hands slightly more than shoulder width apart, bending at the waist.
            Avoid bending the knees (this is called a \'stiff leg\' deadlift) and be sure to keep
            your knees behind your toes. Stand up to an erect position, keeping
            your back tight and your weight on the back of your feet. Slowly return to the starting
            position.\n\nHow to switch it up: Start with your legs farther apart and a narrower grip
            on the bar. This puts more emphasis on hips and quads.</item>
        <item name="lat_pulldown">What you\'ll need: a weight machine.\n\nWhat to do: Grip the bar with your hands farther
            than shoulder width apart (you\'ll most likely have to stand up to do this, and then sit
            down). Pull down by pinching your shoulder blades together, with your back at a slight
            angle. Pull down to chest level, then slowly return to starting position.\n\nHow to switch
            it up: Use a narrower grip, but DO NOT touch the bar to the back of your neck instead
            of your chest. There is no advantage to this and it can be dangerous.</item>
        <item name="squat">What you\'ll need: A barbell (optional).\n\nWhat to do: If using a barbell,
            stand with your back straight and the bar positioned over the back of your neck. Slowly
            move your hips back while bending your knees to lower your upper body. It is important to
            keep your knees behind your feet. Continue until the \'crease\' of your hips is below your
            knees. Return to the standing position.\n\nHow you can switch it up: \'Deep\' squats
            involve lowering the torso even farther towards the floor, but can put more stress on the
            knees, so be careful when doing this.</item>
        <item name="shoulder_press">What you\'ll need: A barbell or dumbbells.\n\nWhat to do: Start with
            your arms at your sides, elbows bent. If using dumbbells, rest them on your shoulders, and
            if using a barbell rest it across the top of your back. Extend your arm fully (reach toward
            the ceiling). Slowly return to the starting position.</item>
        <item name="deadlift">What you\'ll need: A barbell.\n\nWhat to do: Stand behind the barbell, and
            grip it with your hands slightly more than shoulder width apart, bending at the waist.
            Move your knees forward when initially lifting the bar, and back when standing up (unlike
            the \'stiff-leg\' version of the deadlift). Be sure to keep your knees behind your toes.
            Stand up to an erect position, keeping your back tight and your weight on the back of your
            feet. Slowly return to the starting position.\n\nHow to switch it up: Start with your
            legs farther apart and a narrower grip on the bar.</item>
        <item name="tricep_scooop">What you\'ll need: A dumbbell.\n\nWhat to do: Hold a single dumbbell
            above your head in both hands. Position the weight behind your head and slowly lower it
            by bending at the elbows. Lower to the point where it would touch your back, then return
            to the starting position.\n\nHow you can switch it up: A bench press done with a narrow
            grip (hands close together) works the same muscles.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>